[{"answer": "Well, that's not clear at this point, or we just don't know those details yet.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Was this guy a sleeper put into al Qaeda in the Yemen by the CIA or was it another twist?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "ASTINGS: Well, first I think you look at it, Yemen has become the hot new battleground in the war on terror.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "What do you make of two things, I guess, one, the more sophisticated bomb that they were working on, but secondly, this whole notion, potentially of having sleepers, agents inside al Qaeda now?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, it's clearly a big intelligence success for the Americans, for the Saudis.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Why wouldn't they reveal all the details?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "They must have been in a state of panic.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "What would you imagine is going on now within al Qaeda as an overall organization?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, it's not just me, but North Carolina, as it looks like 60 percent of the voters there are poised to adopt the state amendment.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Mr. Perkins, tell me why are you so implacably opposed to two loving people getting married?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I think that's a really question and I think a lot of people will ask that question of themselves, because quite frankly, marriage from -- among heterosexuals has not been good, when we see a divorce rate around 50 percent.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "You treat it as a celebrity bag extension?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Yes, again, Piers, you're asking great questions because I think those are the questions that are going through people's minds.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "How much more damage can a gay couple do if they're married to the damage they can do to civilization if they're unmarried?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "You have five kids, right?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Well, we would have a conversation about it.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What would you do if one of them came home and said, dad, I'm gay?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I'm struggling to contain my excitement.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Are you ready for round two, Jonah?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Who knows.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "I might come out a rabid fascist after the break, who knows?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "I'm glad you brought this up, because the one question you asked me on the last show about my book, I gave you the answer, and I said look, liberals and conservatives are like our ideological but conservatives admit it.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "I promise you were coming to this in detail but on the premise of liberal cliches, is it not a right-wing cliche to assume that anyone that disagrees with you on any kind o matter automatically has to be a screaming liberal?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "I said you tried to bully me, I didn't say you bullied me.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Then you must be -- you must be the least bulliable person ever created, aren't you?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Look, I think we have a misunderstanding about ideology.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "If I was a liberal responding to the allegation that essential to your block, I'd say, come on, Jonah, where is your ideology about gay marriage?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "It was FDR --", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Is this another cheap bit of liberal cliche riddled nonsense?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Well, one of my great frustrations when I speak on college campuses, in particular, is how so many kids are taught to be deeply skeptical of ideological statements, but they'll let these cliches just sort sail right through.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What really compelled you to write this book?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "In terms of better 10 guilty men go free, right, if you look at it as an ideological statement, I have no problem with it.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Well, what is wrong with those two -- what is wrong with those two statements?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Sure, absolutely.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "And doesn't that inevitably lend to a more cliche ridden game?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "They can often be just as bad about as Democrats.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "But to sum up, Republicans are as bad at this as Democrats, right?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "But can I assume what you're about to tell me is out of character?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, I am here.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Are you just trying to win the record for the most plugs in one minute?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Because it started off with -- I believed in him.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Did you mean what you said about -- why do you feel so exercised about this tax issue?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Maybe some of it, but not all of it.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "You don't think people that ran Wall Street are responsible for a lot of the economic meltdown this country had to suffer?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Well, that's wrong, yes.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Who is more responsible, the very, very smart people who know exactly what they are offering or the people who are perhaps not so smart, not so well versed in the property market, in loans, in finance generally, who get seduced into accepting these and then lose everything?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "But who is more responsible?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "And what is wrong with taxing the super rich a little bit more then the super poor?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "A lot, a lot more than they're saying.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "How many are disaffected with Obama, do you think?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Yeah, but I didn't argue that point.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Why shouldn't it?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Yes, but he's putting people on the defensive.", "docId": "120508pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Would they?", "qSentId": 598}]